theconstructioncentre.co.uk 2011-12-31

# The Construction Centre - Privacy

## The Construction Centre Privacy Policy and Disclaimer

This Privacy Policy sets out the data processing practices carried out through the use of the Internet and the World Wide Web by theconstructioncentre.co.uk If you have any requests concerning your personal information or any queries with regard to these practices please contact us at [info@theconstructioncentre.co.uk](mailto:info@theconstructioncentre.co.uk)

### Information collected

theconstructioncentre.co.uk collects personal information from visitors to this web site through the use of online forms and every time you e-mail us your details. We may also collect information automatically about your visit to our web site.

### What information do we collect?

We collect the information necessary to provide the service you request. We will collect your name and address and your e-mail address if you e-mail to us or otherwise provide it. We will collect your URL if you provide it to us.

### What do we use the information for?

We want to give our users the best possible service. We may therefore use the data gathered to contact you to check this is the case. We may use it to advise you by 'phone, fax or e-mail of new possibilities and changes to our service or new services that we or our associated companies offer.

You can opt out of receiving this information by emailing us at [info@theconstructioncentre.co.uk](mailto:info@theconstructioncentre.co.uk), stating your full details and stating that you do not wish to receive any marketing details.

### Use of personal information

theconstructioncentre.co.uk processes personal information collected via this web site for the purposes of:

  * Planning and managing the theconstructioncentre.co.uk business and workload
  * Identifying potential customers or subscribers
  * Carrying out market research
  * Maintaining information as a reference tool or general resource and
  * Providing you with information about products and services we offer

If you do not wish to receive information about theconstructioncentre.co.uk products and services please send an email to [info@theconstructioncentre.co.uk](mailto:info@theconstructioncentre.co.uk), or call 01926 863004, fax to 01926 863005 or write to us at The Construction Centre, 1 Alpha House, Farmer Ward Road, Kenilworth, CV8 2ED

### Automated information collection

We have a policy of continual improvement of our site. We therefore collect information automatically about your visit to it. This is used to help us see browsing preferences.

### Use of cookies

A cookie is a small piece of information sent by a web server to a web browser, which enables the server to collect information from the browser. Find out more about the use of cookies on [www.cookiecentral.com](http://www.cookiecentral.com/).

theconstructioncentre.co.uk uses "cookies" to identify you when you visit this web site and to keep track of your browsing patterns and build up a demographic profile.

With regards to Google and the [DoubleClick DART cookie](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx) (used to serve ads on this site):

  * Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site.
  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to our users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.co.uk/privacy_ads.html).

### Transferring information abroad

We do not transfer information in this way.

No unauthorised copying or other such use of this policy is permitted.

### Disclaimer (for visitors)

theconstructioncentre.co.uk does not provide advice. These pages therefore contain general information only. We have made comments on the sites shown. They are our honest opinion and any facts given are true to the best of our knowledge and belief. However, before taking any step important to you, you should rely wholly on your own enquiries and take advice where appropriate.

We do not endorse or approve the content of any third party site.

We will not have liability in connection with:

  * Any third party site
  * Any suggestion that the third party site breaks any law or regulation or in any other way infringes your rights 
  * We make no warranty or representation about: 
  * Anything contained in or promised by any website referred to in this site or that can be accessed by hyperlink (or otherwise) from this site. 
  * Anything contained on this site 

**The Construction Centre is a trading name of UK250 Limited, 2 Alpha House, Farmer Ward Road, Kenilworth, CV8 2ED.**
